我看的杂志中的女孩多数可都是裸体的
Girls in my magazines are a lot nakeder.
嘿,乔伊
Oh,hey,Joey.
-嘿 -我有点事要跟你商量
- Hey. - Listen,I need to ask you something.
你还记得我继父在监狱里的事吧?
You know how my stepdad's in prison?
-嗯 -嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
嗯，这个周末他本来有个假期的 这样明天他就能来参加我的婚礼了
He was supposed to get a weekend furlough so he could go to the wedding.
但是他刚刚打电话来说，嗯
But he just called and..
他实在忍不到周一就在操场上捅了一个送冰的家伙
Well,apparently stabbing lceman in the exercise yard couldn't wait till Monday.
- 这么说他来不了了吗? - 对。
- So he can't come? - No.
这么一来就没人挽着我走过红地毯了。 所以，嗯...
And so there's no one to walk me down the aisle. And..
嗯，我很希望你能挽着我
Well,I would just really love it if you would do it.
-真的? -对
- Seriously? - Yeah.
你知道，一直以来我都把你当作父亲一样
You've,you know,sort of been like a dad to me.
我是说，你一直以来都很照顾我， 和我一起分享你的智慧
You've always,you know,looked out for me and shared your wisdom.
我的确很有智慧。
I am pretty "wisdomous."
所以...你觉得呢?
So,what do you say?
当然，这是我的荣幸，菲比
Are you kidding? Phoebe,I would be honored.
哦，谢啦。
Oh,thank you.
我希望
I hope..
你能够了解你对我来说有多么重要。
I hope you know how much you mean to me.
听着，我希望
Listen,I hope..
我希望你知道......
I hope that you know..
我不想让你看到爸爸哭的样子 回自己的房间去!
I don't want you to see your father cry. Go to your room!
菲比的婚礼
The.One.With.Phoebe's.Wedding
哦,不不不,让你爸付吧
Oh,no,no,no. Let your dad get this.
哦，是我的婚礼策划人。她快把我逼疯了。
It's my wedding planner. She's driving me crazy!
喂，嘿， 行了行了，别这么大声嚷嚷!
Hello? Okay,stop screaming!
好,那就比目鱼好了。
Okay,so halibut.
好吧，三文鱼也行,随便什么都好。
All right,so salmon. Either way. I don't..
-我无所谓。 -可我有所谓!
- It doesn't matter to me. - Well,it matters to me!
好吧，我不在乎，听你的好了。
Well,I don't care. So you pick.
你刚才挂我的电话?
Did you just hang up on me?
好了，听着，我要你在1800点整的时候准时到达婚礼彩排的现场。
All right,look,I need you at the rehearsal dinner tonight at 1800 hours.
哦，好,那是几点钟啊?
Okay. What time is that?
你不知道军用时刻吗?
You don't know military time?
哦，当时我在接受导弹训练，所以没学到。
I must have been in missile training the day they taught that.
减12就行了。
Just subtract 12.
噢， 那1800减去12
Okay,so 1800 minus 12..
就是1788。
is 1788.
- 6点钟! -噢！.
- Six o'clock! - Okay.
哦，等一下。好,我是盖勒
Hold on. Yeah? Geller here.
不,我说过了，一定要在4点之前送到。 再见。
No,I said it has to be there by 4:00. Goodbye.
天哪，做一个冰雕有那么难么?
How hard is it to make an ice sculpture?
比看起来难！
Harder than it looks.
冰雕? 太隆重了吧。
Wait. Ice sculpture? That sounds really fancy.
我跟你说过我只想要一个简单的婚礼就好。
I told you,I just want a simple wedding.
放心好了,亲爱的。一切都包在我身上。
Please,honey,leave the details to me.
为了你，我会尽量把这一天弄得特别一些。
Now,I wanna make this day as special for you as I can.
好了,我打算让竖琴师穿成白色。
I was thinking the harpist should wear white.
竖琴师? 不是我朋友马崔来敲钢鼓的吗?
Harpist? My friend Marjorie is playing the steel drums.
-哦,她退出了。 -她退出了? 为什么?
- Oh,she backed out. - She did? Why?
我叫她这么做的。
I made her.
钢鼓和高雅的婚礼不太搭调
Steel drums don't really say "elegant wedding."
-而且马崔的体味太浓了。 -嘿!
- Nor does Marjorie's overwhelming scent. - Hey!
西藏独立之后她才会洗澡的。
She will shower when Tibet is free.
-嘿。你看起来真美。 - 你也是。
- Hey. You look great. - You too.
真高兴能有彩排，我打算在把这些食物吃下去之前演习一下。
I'm glad we're having a rehearsal dinner. I rarely practice my meals before I eat.
嘿,还记得你答应过要送给我们的礼物是什么吗？
What did we say was your one gift to us?
不开无聊的玩笑。 我以为那只是在正式的婚礼上。
No stupid jokes,but I thought that was for the actual wedding.
先演习一下吧。
Rehearse it.
嗨。
Hi.
-真高兴你们都来了。 -哦,我...
- Thanks for coming,you guys. - Oh,yeah..
我只打算握个手。
I was.. I was going for a handshake.
所以你把手顶在我的裤裆上?
That why your hand's against my crotch?
-没错。 -好了
- That is why. - Yeah.
瑞秋，艾玛呢？
So,Rach,where's Emma?
哦,莫妮卡让我把她送到我妈那里去了。
Monica made me send her to my mom's.
显然，婴儿和婚礼可掺合不到一块儿。
Apparently,babies and weddings don't mix.
你还在为你那烦人的小家伙哭哭啼啼的?
Are you still crying about your damn baby?
菲比,待会儿在致酒时你要说快点。 记住，跟每个人都是20秒。
Phoebe,you got to keep the line moving. Remember,20 seconds per person.
你和这些家伙天天见面，没什么可说的
You see these clowns all the time.
你最好把婚礼策划人的名字给我
You must give me the name of your wedding planner.
我真想把紧张的舞会抛开
I wanna throw a really tense party.
-嘿,你们是麦克的父母吧? -是的。
- Hey,you're Mike's parents,right? - Yes,we are.
眼看着我们的小家伙们都长这么大了，是吧？
Our little ones are growing up fast,aren't they?
-你说什么? -你知道…
- How's that? - You know..
一方面替他们高兴，但另一方面心里又有点舍不得。
on one hand,you're happy for them. On the other,it's hard to let go.
你想怎么把假日给分开过呢?
How do you want to divide up the holidays?
我想感恩节在我家,圣诞在你家
I was thinking Thanksgiving at my place,Christmas at yours.
你到底贵姓啊?
Who in God's name are you?
我也不喜欢你们，老兄，我是看在孩子们的面子上才跟你们客气的。
I'm not that fond of you either,buddy. I'm just trying to be nice for the kids.
你知道我刚想起什么吗? 咱俩还没有被分配在婚礼上的任务呢。
You know what? We have no idea what we're doing in the wedding tomorrow.
我觉得咱们会是伴郎。但是现在他们怎么还不跟咱俩说呢?
I thought we'd be groomsmen. They would have asked us by now.
你什么时候知道你是伴娘的?
When did they ask you to be a bridesmaid?
-呃... 11月? -我觉得情况有点不妙。
- November. - I wanna say it's not looking good.
- 嘿,菲比！ - 干吗?
- Hey,Phoebe? - Sorry?
呃,你还没有告诉他们俩在婚礼上要做什么呢。
You haven't told these guys what they're doing in the wedding yet.
哦,那个,他们不会出现在婚礼仪式上。
Well,they're not in the wedding.
什么?
What?
呃
Well..
气氛有点尴尬。
this is really awkward.
哦,这儿没我的事儿了。
Oh,and I can leave.
真对不起你们，但麦克有一个哥哥 而且还有他在学校的死党
I'm sorry,you guys. But Mike's got his brother and his friends from school.
所以...如果这么说
So,you know,you were..
能让你们好受一点,你们两个是头号候补，就差那么一点。
If it helps,you were next in line. You just missed the cut.
哦,天哪.
Oh,man.
以前在选花样滑冰队员（女子运动项目） 的时候就是这样。
This is like figure skating team all over again.
我是说，水上芭蕾（还是女子运动项目）
I mean,synchronized swimming.
我的意思是，平衡木（仍旧是女子运动项目）
I mean.. I mean,the balance beam.
-帮帮忙. -橄榄球!
- Help me. - Football.
谢了。
Thank you.
噢,菲比,赶快吐出来。那里面有猪肉。
Oh,Phoebe,spit that out. That has pork in it.
我记得那个砂锅应该是全素的。
I thought the pot stickers were supposed to be vegetarian?
啊,是的，但我做了点变动。 我发传真告诉你了。
Yeah,I changed them. I sent you a fax about it.
可是我根本没有传真机啊。
I don't have a fax machine.
哈! 那你可能会发现有一些意外。
Well,then there are gonna be a few surprises.
我简直不敢相信 只有我们俩不会出现在仪式上。
I can't believe we're gonna be the only people not in the wedding.
-是啊，我讨厌被冷落。 -要知道这是一个婚礼!
- I know. I hate being left out of things. - And it's a wedding.
如果缺了我感觉会很奇怪的。
It'll be weird if I'm not in it.
-嘿,你们俩怎么样? -还好啦。
- Hey,guys,how's it going? - Fine.
坐在这，就我们俩，无所事事。我们在为明天做彩排呢。
We're sitting here,alone,doing nothing. It's our rehearsal for tomorrow.
嘿，关于明天，我有个问题问你们。
Look,about tomorrow,I've got a question for you.
我刚知道我的一个伴郎出了点急事， 所以不能来了。
I found out one of my groomsmen had an emergency and can't make it.
- 出什么事了? - 管那么多干嘛! 所以...?
- What happened? - Who cares? And..?
所以我在想，也许你们两个人中的一个能...
And I was wondering if one of you guys..
- 我来替他! - 不,我!
- I'll do it! - Me!
你们两个都想做? 呃,只有一个名额。
You both wanna do it? There's only room for one.
选我! 我适合穿燕尾服 而且我这模样也不会抢你的镜头。
Pick me. I look great in a tux,and I won't steal focus.
不,麦克,不。选我! 我的意思是,瞧!
No,Mike. No,no,you wanna pick me. I mean.. Watch.
呃,我不太习惯来做这种决定。
You know,I really don't feel very comfortable making this decision.
菲比更了解你们 我会让她来选。
You know,Phoebe knows you better. I'm gonna let her choose.
嗯，如果是菲比来选的话,你现在就可以跟麦克的新伴郎打招呼了。
Well,if Phoebe's choosing,then say hello to Mike's next groomsman.
哦,我会的。但我要先找一面镜子
Oh,I will. But I will need a mirror..
因为这个人就是我。
as he is me.
- 省省吧,你逊死了。 - 你更逊.
- Please. You're going down. - You are going "downer."
他们在选花样滑冰队员的时候就是这么说你的？
They say that on the figure skating team?
我不知道，我没被选上。
I wouldn't know. I didn't make it.
明天我会扮演菲比的继父,你知道吧?
You know I'm filling in for Phoebe's stepdad tomorrow,right?
-知道。很感谢你能这么做。 -哦，嘿，这是我的荣幸。
- Yeah. Yeah. Hey,thanks for doing that. - Oh,hey,my pleasure.
那好，你对我的菲比有什么企图?
So,what are your intentions with my Phoebe?
-我“企图”跟她结婚。 -哦，自作聪明的人。
- I intend to marry her. - Oh,a wiseacre.
照我的理解，你似乎打算靠弹钢琴来养活老婆
I understand you plan to support your wife by playing the piano?
这种工作好像不太稳定。
Isn't that kind of unstable?
-哦，跟演戏比起来还算好啦。 -第二次攻击。
- No more so than acting. - Strike two.
你说得对。我可能需要她来养活。
You're right. She probably will support me.
嘿,除非我们搬去跟你一起住,爸爸。
Hey,unless we move in with you,Dad.
第三次攻击。
Strike three.
你只有最后一次机会了，麦克。
You only get one more,Mike.
-麦克,我能和你聊聊吗? -可以,当然
- Michael,can I see you for a moment? - Yeah,sure.
那真是..
This was..
太怪了
weird.
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
脸色怎么这么差?
What's with the face?
那个麦克不尊重人.我不知道他怎么这样
That Mike has got no respect. I'm not sure about him.
等下,那不是他,他在这
Wait,that's not him. There he is.
怎么样? 你决定了没有?
So? What did you decide?
我决定...要去厕所。
I decided to pee.
你要在我们两个人里选一个来参加仪式。
You have to choose one of us to be in your wedding.
-有个伴郎来不了了 -哦,不。
- One of the groomsmen fell out. - Oh,no,no.
你们两个叫我怎么选啊。你们对我来说同样重要。
I can't choose between you two. I love you both so much.
的确重要，差一点就能参加原定的婚礼了。
Just not enough to put us in the original wedding party.
真差劲
Such bitterness.
最好把这态度留到婚礼
Best to keep that attitude in the seats.
来吧,菲比.我们都想参加,而且由你来决定
Come on,Phoebe. We both really want to do this,and it's up to you.
我没法选。这太...
But I don't wanna choose. It's..
哦,等一下。瑞秋！
Okay,wait. Rach?
呃,我需要你作为伴娘替我选样东西。
Listen,I have a very special bridesmaid task for you to do.
太棒了! 选什么?
Goody! What is it?
嗯,现在伴郎有一个空缺
Well,there's a spot open for only one groomsman..
你需要在罗斯和钱德中间选一个 所以...祝你好运。
and you have to choose between Ross and Chandler. So good luck with that.
什么,什么? 不,不要,我不想选这个。
What? What,what,what? No,I don't wanna do that.
好吧,我想我只好去另找一个新的伴娘了。
I guess I have to find a new bridesmaid.
我来!
I'll do it!
好,现在是2100点。
Okay,it's 2100 hours.
-到你敬酒的时间了。 -我能不能先去一下洗手间?
- Time for your toast. - Do I have time to go to the bathroom?
你的小便时间是2030点。 要专时专用,麦克.
You had a bathroom break at 2030. Pee on your own time,Mike.
关于致酒词，要尽量简短一些。
In regards to the toasts,okay,you wanna keep them short.
婚礼彩排的时候 没有什么比又臭又长的致酒词更烦人了。
Nothing kills a rehearsal dinner like long speeches. Okay.
你要做的就是：上场，干活，然后走人。
You just get in,do your thing,and get out.
你跟钱德也这么说?
Is that what you say to Chandler?
现在已经2101点了,而且我一点也不觉得好笑。
It's 2101,and I am not amused.
好吧
Okay.
新郎和新娘要说几句。
The bride and groom have a few words they'd like to say.
嗨，大家好
Okay. Hello,everyone.
很高兴各位今晚能够光临。 明天就是正式的婚礼了。
And thank you all for being here tonight. So tomorrow's the big event.
大家可能还不知道，我和麦克的开始 一点也不精彩。
Some of you might not know,but Mike and I didn't get off to the best start.
呃,是这样的。
Yeah. My friend Joey and I..
当时乔伊和我决定相互替对方介绍朋友。
decided to fix each other up with friends. So I..
所以呢,我,我...
Oh,okay. I..
我... 我考虑把我的朋友玛丽埃伦介绍给他。
I thought about it,and I fixed him up with my friend Mary Ellen..
玛丽埃伦今晚没有来，因为她
who couldn't be here tonight,because.. It's not..
这不重要，她正在戒毒
It's not important. Well,she's in rehab.
总之呢,乔伊说他要介绍他的朋友麦克给我认识
Anyway. So Joey said that he was fixing me up with his friend Mike..
但他并没有朋友叫麦克，所以就把我的麦克带去了
only he didn't have a friend Mike,so he just brought my Mike.
然后...
And.. And..
尽管如此... 呃,结果呢，结果还不错。
But despite,you know.. It got good.
我想用一点时间来缅怀我的母亲。她今晚不能出席
I wanna take a moment to mention my mother,who couldn't be here.
哦,天哪。
Oh,God.
呃,缅怀时间结束。好了， 呃...
And.. And moment's over.
哦,这个就不说了,然后...
So okay.. Oh,no,forget that.
我可以跳过这里,这个很有意思
I can forget that. Oh,this is funny.
哦但首先你得知道...
Oh,but you need to know that to get that.
哦,好吧，我...
So.. Oh,well,okay.
我...
I.. Okay.
好了，莫妮卡,我再也受不了了!
Okay,Monica,I can't do it like this!
这是我的婚礼! 知道吗？我不需要这样
This is my wedding,okay? I don't want this..
或者这样,或者这样,好吗？
Or this.. Or this..
我要的只是一个简单的婚礼
Okay? I just wanted a simple wedding..
我要我的未婚夫能够随心所欲地上厕所!
where my fiance can go to the bathroom any time he wants!
-你知道吗，你完了。 -什么?
- You know what? You're done. - What?
你被炒了!
You're fired!
干杯!
Cheers.
- 嘿! - 新婚快乐!
- Hey. - Happy wedding day.
我的新婚也祝你快乐。
Happy my wedding day to you.
乔伊，听着,从现在开始这里是伴娘的地盘，好吗?
Joey,listen,this is gonna be bridesmaid central,all right?
我们要在卫生间里面做头发，然后...
We're gonna have hair and makeup in the bathroom.
哦,我要把冰箱里的东西挪一下 给胸花腾出地方。
I had to move a couple things in the fridge to make room for the corsages.
噢,真是的! 早知道有胸花我就不吃早饭了。
Man! I wouldn't have had breakfast if I knew there was gonna be corsages.
嗨
Hi.
关于昨晚,
About last night..
我知道你压力很大，所以...
I know you're under a lot of stress,and..
尽管你说的话让我有点伤心
Well,even though the things you said were a little hurtful to me..
作为一个从未被解雇的人..
as someone who's never been fired before..
高中时是什么感觉..
What about in high school..
当卖酸奶的小店让你做样品招牌?
when that yogurt store let you go for sampling toppings?
大伙都这么做
Everyone there did that.
对啊!但是不是每个人都在暑假结束时赚了3000块
Yeah,but did everybody owe 3 grand at the end of the summer?
我的意思是...
My point is..
好吧,我愿意复职。
Well,I'm willing to take my job back.
哦,还是算了吧。
Oh,well,that's okay.
我觉得如果你只做伴娘的话情况会好得多。
I think you and I will do much better if you're just here as a bridesmaid.
哦，既然你这么说
Is that so?
好吧
Okay.
如果你真这么想的话，好吧
If that's really what you want,then here.
给你这个耳机。我还是不太想给你这个耳机。
I give you the headset. I don't really wanna give you the headset.
还有就是，如果你要接手的话 你大概需要回复这些信息。
I guess if you're taking over,then you should probably return these messages.
哇,真不少啊。
This is a lot.
我相信你能处理它们。 我是说，尽管
But I'm sure you can handle this. I have won awards..
我曾经获得过组织技能的证书，但是呢 我相信你肯定没问题。
for my organizational skills. But I'm sure you'll do fine.
-你获得过证书? -是我用自己的电脑打印出来的.
- You've won awards? - I printed them out on my computer.
- 嘿。 - 嗨。
- Hey. - Hi.
- 瑞秋呢？ -她在自己的房间,有事吗?
- Where's Rach? - She's in her room. Why?
我要跟她谈谈关于那个伴郎的问题
I have to talk to her about this groomsman situation.
我可不想像个傻子一样坐在那儿 看着钱德在婚礼上露脸。
I'm not gonna watch Chandler up there while I'm in the seats like some chump.
这可不是你的婚礼
This wedding isn't about you.
不是吗?那是谁的啊?
It's not? Then who's it about?
好吧,这婚礼曾经和我有关 但现在我也不知道了
Well,it used to be about me,but now I have no idea.
啊,天哪,你简直美得令人窒息。
My God,you're breathtaking.
你想干嘛?
What do you want?
你还没决定伴郎的人选吧?
You haven't by any chance chosen a groomsman yet,have you?
哦,罗斯,求你了。 我已经很为难了，你就别再添乱了。
Ross,please don't make this harder than it already is.
我没有啊。我是在让事情简单化,选我!
I'm not. I'm making it easier. Pick me.
可是,钱德也说这个机会对他十分重要。
Chandler said it's important to him too.
抱歉,你和钱德出去过吗?
I'm sorry,did you and Chandler go out?
你和钱德曾经抱过吗?
Do you and Chandler have a huge history,huh?
你和钱德有孩子吗?
Do you and Chandler have a child together?
如果我说是,就会让你发疯,是不是?
If I said yes that would freak you out,wouldn't it?
听着听着
Listen. Listen.
无论你选谁，你要知道 你选的这个人将要跟你一起走过红地毯
Whoever you pick is gonna walk down the aisle with you.
我可以保证，到时候我一个字也不会说 但如果你选钱德的话
Now,I promise I won't say a word. But if you pick Chandler..
他肯定会一直在你耳朵旁边嘀咕他那些无聊的玩笑。
he's gonna be whispering stupid jokes in your ear the whole time.
哦.....两个恶魔里你确实好一点..
Oh,you are the lesser of two evils.
没错
Yes!
先别跟钱德说,我来和他说
Don't say anything to Chandler until I talk to him.
-明白了 -好
- You got it. - Okay.
真不相信你居然拿艾玛来说事
I cannot believe you played the Emma card.
行了!我把自己的身体都献给你了
Oh,please. I was prepared to offer you my body.
喔天啊!我竟然没阻止你
Oh,my God! And I didn't hold out.
你知道,那通常都会伤我的感情..
You know,normally,that would hurt my feelings..
但是今天,我是伴郎
but today,I'm a groomsman.
塞文,我不知道你在说什么。 花又有什么问题了?
Sven,I don't understand what you're saying. What is wrong with the flowers?
Lorkins? Lorkins是什么见鬼的玩意?
"Lorkins"? What the hell are "lorkins"?
我知道。
I know.
-嘿. -嘿,麦克,如果你是瑞典人
- Hey. - Mike,if you were Swedish..
你用lorkins来代表一种花,会是什么花呢?
and you were saying the word "lorkins," what flower would that be?
-兰花(Orchids)? -真棒
- Orchids? - Right there!
我就是因为这个才嫁给你的。
That's why I'm marrying you.
你好,麦克尔（麦克的全名）.
Hello,Michael.
乔瑟夫（乔伊的全名）.
Joseph.
我能跟你说两句吗?
May I have a word with you,please?
你想站那里说吗?
You wanna step it up there?
这里真是...
This is..
棒极了。
great.
坐。
Have a seat.
昨天晚上,
Last night..
我试着欢迎你进入我们的家族。
I tried to welcome you into my family.
然而，你对我很不尊重
And instead,you disrespect me.
我不能容忍这一点。
I cannot allow this.
你是在排练什么劣制黑手党电影吗?
Are you rehearsing for some really bad Mafia movie?
还敢顶嘴。
More back talk.
没错，我也许是从我没有成功的《家族荣誉2》的
And yes,I may be borrowing a few lines from my recent unsuccessful audition..
试镜剧本中挑了两句。
for Family Honor 2: This A-Time It's A-Personal.
乔伊,我今天比较忙 你到底想要干嘛?
Joey,I kind of have a lot to do today. What do you want?
我想要你认真一点。
I want you to take this seriously!
菲比对我来说非常非常的重要,知道吗？
Phoebe is very,very important to me,okay?
我要你保证，你会好好照顾她。
I wanna make sure you are gonna take care of her.
乔伊,我爱菲比
Joe,I love Phoebe.
在我的生命中没有什么比她更重要。
She's the most important thing in my life.
我宁死也不会让她受到任何伤害。
I'd die before I let anything happen to her.
这才是我想听的。
That's what I wanted to hear.
因为我当她是家里人，知道吗？
Because she's family,okay?
现在你也要成为家里的一份子了。
And now you're gonna be family.
在世界上没有什么事比家庭更重要。
And there's nothing more important in the whole world than family.
那个电影可真是烂得可以。
That must have been one lousy movie.
不是台词，是我说的!
That was me!
-嘿 -嘿,我能跟你商量一下伴郎的事吗？
- Hi. - Let's talk about this groomsman thing.
如果你选罗斯,你知道的 你们俩只能安安静静地走过红地毯。
If you pick Ross,he'll walk you down the aisle just fine.
但如果你选我的话
But if you choose me..
你可就有笑话听了。
you'll be getting some comedy.
即便如此
Even so..
我想我还是选罗斯
I think I'm gonna pick Ross.
没错,我觉得你可能..
Yeah,I figured you might..
因为过去,而且你曾经爱过他..
because of the history,and you used to love him..
而且还生了个孩子
and you guys have a baby.
那么就谢谢你尊重我的决定了
Well,thank you for respecting my decision.
我来告诉你为什么你要选我。
Let me tell you why you need to pick me.
当我还是个孩子的时候，无论做什么 我总是被冷落的一个。
See,when I was a kid,you know,I was always left out of everything..
你要知道，这种经历总是让我缺乏安全感。
and it really made me feel insecure.
在运动场上我永远都是被人家挑剩下的那个
I was always picked last in gym..
甚至落后于那个交换学生，连棒球规则也不懂的胖子
even behind that fat exchange student who didn't know the rules to baseball.
那个家伙一打着球，撂下球棒就朝三垒上跑。
I mean,this guy would strike out and then run to third.
真是太耻辱了
It's just so humiliating.
我是说,你应该知道被排在万事之外的感觉,对吧?
I mean,you know how it feels to be left out of things,right?
- 不 - 不
- No. - No.
总之，如果我成为唯一一个不能参加婚礼的人
Anyway,if I'm the only one left out of this wedding..
以前那些凄惨的回忆就会再次浮现在眼前。
I just know that all those feelings are gonna come rushing back.
好吧，我选你。
All right,fine,I pick you.
太棒了！
Yes!
终于有钱德的房间了。 (“伴郎”与“房间”谐音)
Make "groom" for Chandler.
噢,我的天哪!
Oh,my.
不,要照我说的做。 因为你的办法太笨了。
No,we're gonna do it my way. Because your way is stupid.
好了，有电话正打进来，我要挂了，牧师。
All right,I got to go. I have another call,Reverend.
喂。
Hello?
- 这次小小的谈话还算愉快。 - 是啊,没错。
- I'm glad we had this little talk. - Yes.
对了，谢谢你关于新婚之夜的那些建议。
And thanks for all the wedding night advice.
我一点都不觉得尴尬。
That didn't make me uncomfortable at all.
好了，就这样吧。大家晚上见喽。
All right,so I'll see everybody tonight.
- 好 - 再见
- Okay. - Bye.
呃,你们知道在走廊里有个大号的冰雕么？
Did you guys know that there's a giant ice sculpture in the hall?
哦天哪，为什么会在这儿的？
Oh,my God,what's it doing here?
呃,我猜是送货的家伙把投递地址和付款人地址搞混了。
I guess it got sent to the billing address as opposed to the shipping address.
-哦,真是个蠢货! -我的天哪! 什么事都是一团糟。
- What a pickle. - Oh,my God,everything's such a mess.
为什么这些事情会发生在我身上？
Why is this happening to me?
你们想不想用舌头去舔舔它?
How bad do you wanna stick your tongue on that?
-你怎么样? -我很好啊。
- How's it going? - Good.
我来要点咖啡喝 这样我能在婚礼上清醒一点。
I'm just getting some coffee so I'm alert for the wedding.
我也是这么打算的。
That's what I was doing too.
那好，今晚玩得高兴点。
Well,you have fun tonight.
- 你也是。 - 哦,我会的。
- You too. - Oh,I will.
我也会的。
Me too.
慢着,我知道自己为什么这么得意 但你为什么也这样？
Wait a minute. I know why I'm being such an ass. Why are you?
-我不能告诉你。 -我也不能告诉你。
- I'm not supposed to tell you. - I'm not supposed to tell you.
瑞秋说过你可以参加婚礼了吗?
Did Rachel say you could be in the wedding?
- 没错 - 她也那么告诉我的
- Yes. - She told me that too!
真不能相信,我打着艾玛的旗号说事
I don't believe this. I played the Emma card.
我审视了自己的灵魂
I looked into my soul.
你同时答应我们两个人参加仪式？
You told us both we could be in the wedding?
我的解释是,你们不应该告诉对方的!
In my defense,you weren't supposed to tell each other!
瑞秋,只有一个人可以参加婚礼仪式。 你必须要选一个。
Rachel,only one of us can do it. You have to choose.
你和我,我们又能在一起了。
You and me together again.
瑞秋，瑞秋,咚,咚敲门声
Rach,Rach? Knock-knock.
- 是谁啊? - 在婚礼上我再告诉你。
- Who's there? - I'll tell you at the wedding.
嘿，我忘拿围巾了。
Hey,I forgot my scarf.
我做不来，我真的不知道应该选谁。
I can't do this. I don't know which one of you guys to pick.
哦，你还没选好呢。我倒是有个好主意。
Oh,you haven't picked yet? Oh,good,because I had an idea.
我觉得如果由我们家的狗恰皮来担任伴郎的话 肯定很有意思。
I thought it would be fun if the third groomsman was my family dog,Chappy.
什么,一只狗? 不,让瑞秋来选。
What? A dog? No. Rachel gets to choose.
真是难以抉择啊。
Wow,this is a tough one.
看起来我只有选那只狗了。
I think I'm gonna have to go with the dog.
等一下，你是说，厨师已经到汉密尔顿俱乐部了
So,what you're saying is that the chef is at the Hamilton Club..
但食物还没有送到？ 饮料和酒水已经送到了，但男招待还没有到？
but the food is not? And the drinks are there but the bartender is not?
你... 他妈的开什么玩笑!?
Are you freaking kidding me?
怎么样了?
How's it going?
- 帮帮我... - 什么?
- Help me. - What?
我想让你做回疯婆子。
I want you to be crazy bitch again.
真的?
Really?
求你了。
Please?
-你真想让我回来? -嗯,胜过我想结婚。
- You really want me to come back? - More than I wanna get married.
好,伙计们,我们回来了。
Okay,people,we are back in business!
哦天哪,我可想死你了。
Oh,God,I have missed you so much. Okay.
好了,去做你的头发吧。 这儿一切交给我好了。
Get your hair and makeup done. I'll take care of everything.
-嘿,你们打算怎么办? -什么怎么办?
- Hey,what are you guys gonna do? - About what?
暴风雪啊。我刚看电视
The blizzard. I just saw on the news..
说这是20年来最大的一场暴风雪。
it's the worst snowstorm in 20 years.
所有的桥和隧道都关闭了。
They already closed all the bridges and tunnels.
可是乐队和摄像师还要从新泽西赶过来呢！
But the band and the photographer are coming in from New Jersey.
看来他们够呛。
I don't think they are.
哈哈,看起来你恐怕也参加不了仪式了吧。
Looks like you're not gonna be in the wedding,either.
真遗憾啊,菲比
So sorry,Phoebe.
-俱乐部停电了。 -是啊，听新闻说，市里大部分地区都停电了。
- Well,the club lost its power. - The news said most of the city did.
-你从什么时候开始看起新闻来了? -呃，告诉你好了
- Since when do you watch the news? - For your information..
从那个靓女开始主持天气预报的时候
since they hired a very hot weather girl.
真不敢相信，你们两个今天的婚礼办不成了。
I can't believe you aren't getting married today.
是啊
I know.
哇，你们看哪，外面真的好美。 你不是总想在户外举行婚礼吗？
It's so beautiful out there. You always wanted to get married outside.
-你们俩干嘛不干脆在街上结婚呢？ -什么?
- Why don't you just do it on the street? - What?
看哪，雪几乎已经停了。
Well,look,it's hardly snowing anymore.
我想，没有比这更加浪漫的布景了。
I mean,you couldn't ask for a more romantic setting.
这不正是你一直想要的简单的婚礼吗？
This could be the simple wedding you've always wanted.
你认为呢?
What do you think?
我只想今天就跟你结婚。
I think I wanna get married to you today.
我也是。莫妮卡,你觉得这样可行吗?
Me too. Monica,do you think we could do it?
赞成。
Affirmative!
好！ 大家把椅子都搬出来。
Okay,let's get these chairs out here!
甘瑟,把圣诞用的灯饰都打亮。
Gunther,hit the Christmas lights.
喂！ 是哪个家伙把冰雕放在热水井旁边的?
Okay,who left the ice sculpture on the steam grate?
- 麦克 - 嘿,你们来了,太棒了. 恰皮!
- Michael. - Hey,you made it. Great. Chappy!
- 对啊 - 嗨
- There you go. - Hi. Hi.
妈妈,我知道在大街上结婚这种事 肯定不合你的脾气...
I know getting married in the street isn't what you approve of.
不，这挺有趣儿的，又是灯又是雪的。 我怎么看都看不够。
No,it's lovely. The lights and the snow. I could look at them forever.
我刚才在她的饮料里下了点药。
I crushed a pill and put it in her drink.
来吧,亲爱的。
Come on,sweetheart.
你们看,恰皮太弱小了恐怕难以应付积雪
You know,Chappy's too small to handle all this snow.
到时候需要有人抱着它。
Someone has to walk him down the aisle.
-那么,这个人也算参加了婚礼仪式吧? - 我想是吧.
- Would this person be in the wedding? - I guess.
- 我来。 - 我来。
- I'll do it! - I'll do it!
等等，钱德，你不是害怕狗吗?
Chandler,hello? I mean,aren't you scared of dogs?
谁说我害怕。我只要抱着小恰皮 然后...
I'm not scared. I'll just take little Chappy and..
它知道我害怕它!  我的嗓子都翻出来了!
He can sense my fear! My throat is exposed!
哦,那么我猜 C 出现在婚礼上的人就是我喽。哈哈!
I guess I'm in the wedding then.
好臭。
You stinks.
一级警报! 重复,一级警报,这不是演习!
Level one alert! I repeat,level one,this is not a drill!
我们碰到难题了,牧师刚才打电话来说 他被大雪困住，赶不过来了。
We have a situation. The minister called. He's snowed in,he can't make it.
-哦，不是吧。 -嘿,不用担心。
- Oh,no. - Hey,don't worry.
-我在你们结婚那会儿获得的牧师资格到现在还有效。 - 真的?
- I'm still ordained from your wedding. - Really?
是啊。你认为我会放弃牧师资格和免费坐地铁吗
Yeah. You think I'd give up being a minister and pay to ride the subway?
部长坐地铁也不能免票的
Ministers don't ride the subway for free.
我仔细研究过圣经的,没错，我们不用买票。
I had to read the Bible pretty carefully,but,yeah,we do.
如果让乔伊来主持婚礼的话 那我们还需要有个人来挽着菲比。
We have to find someone else to walk Phoebe down the aisle.
我来! 啊哈哈...
I'll do it!
好， 麦克和乔伊,各就各位。
Okay,Mike and Joey,get in position.
钱德,跟我来。
Chandler,come with me.
乔伊负责主持婚礼  你由钱德负责。
Okay,Joey's doing the ceremony,and Chandler's giving you away.
哦,好。嗨,新爸爸。
Oh,okay. Hi,new Dad.
那么,你准备好了么?
So you ready to do this?
哦，天哪，这一切都是真的。
Oh,my God. This is really happening.
-哦,菲比,我真替你高兴,亲爱的。 -谢谢
- Phoebe,I'm so happy for you,honey. - Thank you.
我爱你。 等等，不要抱，当心礼服!
I love you. Wait,wait! No hugs! The dresses!
-管它的。 -来吧!
- Oh,what the hell. - Oh,come on.
-我爱你们，亲爱的。 - 我爱你
- I love you guys. - I love you.
好了， 现在倒计时结束。 各小组听我的指令行事。
Okay,it's zero hour! All teams execute on my count!
我们开始吧!
Let's get this bad boy on the road!
我想让你今晚戴着这副耳机上床，你不反对吧?
Is it okay I want you to wear that headset in bed?
呃,根据计划 我的裸体时间被安排在2300。
I have you scheduled for nudity at 2300 hours.
噢耶。
Oh,yeah.
好了,马崔,开始敲吧。
Okay,Marjorie,hit it.
-天哪,罗斯,你就不能先洗个澡吗。 -是狗身上的味!
- Jeez,Ross. You could've showered. - It's the dog.
伴郎,为什么只有你一个人站在这儿? 伴娘呢?
Groomsman? Why are you standing there? Where's your bridesmaid?
我们遇到情况了,伴娘失踪了。
We've got a broken arrow! Bridesmaid down!
噢,是我自己。
Oh,that's me.
- 准备好了么? - 好了
- Ready? - Okay.
哦,等一下,哦,等等。
Oh,wait. Oh,no. Wait.
哇,你不觉得冷吗?
Wow. Aren't you gonna be cold?
我不在乎。
I don't care.
我要做自己的“蓝色”物品（象征新娘纯洁）
I'll be my "something blue."
- 你看起来美极了。 - 谢谢。
- You look beautiful. - Thank you.
天哪
My God.
你不冷吗?
Aren't you freezing?
朋友们，家人们
Friends. Family.
狗
Dog.
感谢你们能够到场来见证这一场天赐的姻缘。
Thank you all for being here to witness this blessed event.
冷空气已经蔓延到我“那里”了
The cold has now spread to my special place..
所以我会长话短说。
so I'm gonna do the short version of this.
菲比和麦克是完美的一对儿。
Phoebe and Mike are perfect for each other.
我相信在场的每一个人都会和我一样
And I know I speak for everyone here..
祝愿他们一生幸福。
when I wish them a lifetime of happiness.
愿他们有很多孩子..
And may they have many children..
能够为家族的荣誉而报仇
who will one day avenge their family's honor.
我怎么没得到那部分台词?愚蠢的拉尔夫・麦奇奥（《家族荣誉》主演）
How could I not get that part? Stupid Ralph Macchio.
好
Right. Okay.
戒指呢？
Who has the rings?
好的
Okay.
在我成长的过程中,我不曾拥有真正的父爱和母爱，
When I was growing up,I didn't have a normal mom and dad..
或者和别人一样拥有一个正常的家庭
or a regular family like everybody else.
我总是觉得自己缺少了些什么
And I always knew that something was missing.
然而现在,我站在这里
But now I'm standing here today..
我知道自己已经得到了自己所需要的一切
knowing that I have everything I'm ever gonna need.
你就是我的家人。
You are my family.
菲比,你是这么的美丽
Phoebe,you are so beautiful.
这么的善良，这么的大方。
You're so kind. You're so generous.
古怪得这么神奇。
You're so wonderfully weird.
和你在一起的每一天都像是一次探险。
Every day with you is an adventure.
我简直不敢相信自己是如此地幸运。
And I can't believe how lucky I am.
我迫不急待地想要和你分享自己的生命 直到永远。
And I can't wait to share my life with you forever.
哦等一下，我忘了说
Oh,wait! Oh,I forgot. And..
我爱你。
I love you.
还有，你的眼睛很漂亮。
And you have nice eyes.
我也爱你。
I love you too.
- 乔伊	 - 怎么了
- Joey? - Yeah?
恰皮的心脏越跳越慢了。
Chappy's heart rate has slowed way down.
菲比
Okay. Phoebe..
你愿意这个男人成为你的丈夫吗?
do you take this man to be your husband?
我愿意。
I do.
麦克,你愿意这个女人成为你的妻子吗?
Mike,do you take this woman to be your wife?
我愿意。
I do.
我现在正式宣布
I now pronounce you..
你们结为夫妻。
husband and wife.
我结婚了!
I got married!
谁递给我件衣服? 我快要冻僵了。
Could someone get me a coat? I'm frigging freezing.
-真是场让人难以置信的婚礼。 -是啊，的确。
- It really was an incredible wedding. - It was.
我真不想让它就那么结束。 嘿…
I kind of don't want it to end. Hey..
你想来喝一杯吗，还有一些胸花可以吃。
you wanna come in for a drink and a bite of corsage?
我很想去，但现在已经2300了
I'd love to,but it's 2300 hours..
我现在要去 经历一次有史以来最有组织的性爱。
and I'm about to have the most organized sex anyone's ever had.
-嘿,罗斯呢? -我不知道。
- Whatever happened to Ross? - I don't know.
大概和那个刚才聊天的辣妹搞在一起了吧。
Maybe he hooked up with that hot girl he talked to.
快点,恰皮,拜托你快点解决了吧,
Come on,Chappy! Do your business!
拉啊!
Make!
我不是做这项工作的。
I did not sign on for this.